(Kevin:)Anyway, man,
I dug the ape movie, Penny.
(Kevin:)And I thought you were, like,
really great in it.
(Howard:)Aw.
(Wil:)You know, I'm in the movie, too.
Yeah, whatever. Penny!
(Kevin:)Penny, how come you're not
in more stuff, man?
(Kevin:)I'd cast you in a minute.
(Penny:)Seriously?
Oh, yeah, man.
(Kevin:)I'm actually in pre-production
on a movie right now.
(Kevin:)Way different
(Kevin:)than anything I've ever
done before.
It's called Clerks 3.
(Kevin:)You should come over
(Kevin:)and read for a part.
(Penny:)Oh, my, I would love that.
(Leonard:)You have a new job.
(Penny:)Well, maybe I can do both.
(Leonard:)I don't think you can do both.
(Penny:)I don't think I asked you.
(Kevin:)Yeah, you tell him, Penny.
(Leonard:)Stay out of it, Kevin Smith.
(Sheldon:)Do you think there comes
a point in life
(Sheldon:)when it stops feeling bad
to be left out of things?
(Amy:)Probably not.
(Amy:)It's an evolutionary advantage
(Amy:)to be included
in group activities.
(Sheldon:)You know what?
(Sheldon:)I used to be a fan of evolution,
(Sheldon:)but I've since evolved,
(Sheldon:)and now I think it's dumb.